

partheev8@gmail.com



https://github.com/partheev

https://partheev.github.io/myprofilepage/

Full Stack Web Developer

Partheev

A guy with self-motivation and passion on Computer Science. I am an engineering 2nd year student who balances the both academics and my passion towards building useful software. I have 2 years of working experience in developing full stack (MERN) web applications.

I follow the best practices and write clean code while working on projects. I prefer to keep other developers in my mind before writing each line of code. I did few Frontend and Backend projects. Currently I have been working on large scale E-Commerce application based on Microservice architecture. I have no industry experience but I have worked with good teams to develop projects and participate in hackathons.

I am really looking forward to work for organizations and collaborating with other developers.

Experience

NOV 2021 - PRESENT

Admin Dashboard/Frontend Personal Project

Beautiful and Responsive UI design. Built with Next.js framework to make SEO friendly as it is very crucial for Ecommerce apps. Secure authentication for admin users. Here, admin users add new products, modify existing products, uploading new photos directly to AWS S3 buckets. As it is a heavy project, I used Typescript to avoid typos.

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

Authentication System/Personal Project

This is secure authentication system which use JWT to sign tokens. APIs to create new users and send signed tokens when user trying to login. Authorization takes place in other respective servers. Scales well and reduce load on server.

Skills

JavaScript • Typescript • React.js • Node.js • Tailwind CSS • MongoDB • PostgreSQL • Full Stack Web Developer • Golang • Database Design • Docker • C++

Education

2020-2022

Computer Science and Technology/G. Pulla Reddy Engineering College, AP, India. CGPA: 9.19